<xml>
<release>
<version>1.0.1.16</version>
<item>
    <type>E</type>
    <problem>Rebrand with Amcom logos</problem>
    <resolution>rebranded by replacing all SDC logos with Amcom</resolution>
</item>
<item>
    <type>E</type>
    <problem>Change installation path to default to D:\Program Files\</problem>
    <resolution>Defaulted install directory to D:\Program Files\Amcom Software\..etc</resolution>
</item>
<item>
    <type>E</type>
    <problem>Reporting updates</problem>
    <resolution>1.Changed report pegging to mark hangups as completed calls.
    2.Rebranded logos with Amcom logos
    3.New version uses the (install directory) \Report Files\ directory to store needed rdlc files for reporting
    4.Reports now have the version of reporting on every page along with an explanation of line items.
    </resolution>
</item>
<item>
    <type>E</type>
    <problem>Grammar updates</problem>
    <resolution>1. Grammar builder now uses grammarConfig.xml as its configuration file. 
    2. Grammar builder now supports continuous and scheduled grammar builds
    3. grammarConfig.xml now ships with better performing queries when selecting data for building a grammar
    (see grammarConfig.xml for inline comments/directions on setting up scheduled grammars. note: The installed service
    will continue to build grammars just like previous versions with continuous builds if left unchanged.
    </resolution>
</item>
<item>
    <type>E</type>
    <problem>Added versioning to SDCISS service</problem>
    <resolution>Since this typicall runs as a service, at the top of every log file or at the beginning of a service start
    the service will log Amcom.SDC.IntelliSpeech.Service 1.0.1.16 indicating the version that is running </resolution>
</item>
</release>
<release>
<version>1.0.1.18</version>
<item>
    <type>B</type>
    <problem>SDCISS installer does not generate the proper report files folder for reporting</problem>
    <resolution>Modified installer to create "Report Files" folder and add in report .rdlc files</resolution>
</item>
</release>
<release>
<version>1.0.1.19</version>
<item>
    <type>B</type>
    <problem>When running SDCISS as a service, the service sporadically does not stop properly</problem>
    <resolution>Found issue in Speech reporting module which was producing an exception. Corrected issue</resolution>
</item>
<item>
    <type>E/B</type>
    <problem>Outbound dialer component was expiring page transactions prematurely</problem>
    <resolution>Found issue to be related to lack of database connectivity when obtaining the threshold period to use for expiring transactions, in condition where the service 
    cannot access the database to obtain the proper configuration value, as a default this value will not be obtained from the app.xml as a back, if the app.xml does not have the
    parameter set, the default of 7 days will be used.</resolution>
</item>
</release>
<release>
<version>1.0.1.24</version>
<item>
    <type>E</type>
    <problem>Add Command Usage reporting on Transfer Report</problem>
    <resolution>Added</resolution>
</item>
<item>
    <type>E</type>
    <problem>Update reports with latest Amcom branding</problem>
    <resolution>Completed</resolution>
</item>
<item>
    <type>B</type>
    <problem>Date range periods produce inaccurate reports</problem>
    <resolution>Found several issues with the rendering of specific date ranges which was causing major total call inaccuracies. New reporting now use the correct time span
    to cover the appropriate weekly date range period  I.e StartDateTime Date X @ 00:00 hours to EndDateTime Date X @ 23:59</resolution>
</item>
<item>
    <type>B</type>
    <problem>Increased the Preferred name column size in the transfer report</problem>
    <resolution>Completed</resolution>
</item>
<item>
    <type>E</type>
    <problem>Added additional Transaction Report call detaul line items</problem>
    <resolution>Added disambiguation failures, No Input on Confirmation Request</resolution>
</item>
</release>
<release>
<version>1.0.1.25</version>
<item>
    <type>E</type>
    <problem>Rally DE7595 Unable to run service on a 64 bit OS</problem>
    <resolution>Resolved by removing accessive dateTime UTC logging which did not serve a purpose</resolution>
</item>
<item>
    <type>B</type>
    <problem>Rally DE7596 Speech Reporting total number of names enabled is not accurate</problem>
    <resolution>Fixed the query logic used to determine the total count but filtering out directory names that are not enabled for speech</resolution>
</item>
</release>
<release>
<version>1.0.1.26</version>
<item>
    <type>B</type>
    <problem>Rally DE7742 Reporting- Force Reports option not producing the same report totals as report viewer\automated reports</problem>
    <resolution>Resolved issue by handling the dateTime formatting properly</resolution>
</item>
</release>
<release>
<version>1.0.1.27</version>
<item>
    <type>B</type>
    <problem>Rally DE7596 Reporting- Total count of enabled names is enaccurate</problem>
    <resolution>The query used to about the totals was only using the directory.SS_Enable flag, added directory.ss_flag to the query logic</resolution>
</item>
</release>
<release>
<version>1.0.1.28</version>
<item>
    <type>B</type>
    <problem>Rally US26846 Reporting- Removing TEMP Folder and special MyDocuments folder dependencies</problem>
    <resolution>Removed all referrences to Temp or MyDocuments special folders, replaces referrences with the RenderedReportLocation path which is configurable and used for all reporting file output</resolution>
</item>
</release>
</xml>